[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_00_B",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Old Stone Remembers",
        "Description": "Desperate for a way to banish the cruel voice in your head, follow the rambling musings of the old hermit Yonas by seeking the the wisdom of old stone carvings.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What do you know of Corruption?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Only those who seek misery would ask such a thing. You should banish your misery, like I have banished mine. \\n\\nIf you do not, only terrible things can come of it.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Words immortalized in stone. It helps trap the ghosts… ghosts of remembering.\\n\\nCan you remember what I knew?",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I hear my own voice, faint but in chorus with the ghosts here. \\n\\nMy hands on the stone. My memories given to the land and taken from my soul… a mercy, perhaps?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Grace_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01B",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Strength of a Soul",
        "Description": "Prove your resolve to Yonas by enduring a trial by combat in an ancient Soulwarden temple.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"A way to defeat Corruption?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "A valiant effort to stem the tide, perhaps, or more likely to simply take a stand against the inevitable. \\n\\nThere are no final answers here, nor anywhere, but it may yet be a reprieve for one who has been marked such as you.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You will know when you have found your resolve. Until then, I have nothing more to offer you.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well, imagine the kinds of people you run into on the roads around here. \\n\\nBut you're looking a little haggard, if you don't mind me saying so. Had an eventful journey, have you?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01B",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Rumor Has It",
        "Description": "Yonas appears to have left you at the ruins, but luckily Grace O'Malley saw him pass by toward the town of Oxboro. Ask around to see if anyone has seen where he went off to.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Yes. Did you see an old man?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Now that you mention it, there was an old codger a few paces back. They’ve got a proper city that direction. I'll be going back soon enough. \\n\\nBut if you want to go after this geezer, go that way, and just ask around town.",
        "InProgressResponse": "A lot can be gleaned from the locals. Especially when it comes to strangers.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I would ask you to walk softly, but the fish are already wise to me. \\n\\nTravel on, stranger.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 19,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Last Soulwarden",
        "Description": "Seek answers about the Soulwardens' fate within the tower Arcturus.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You abandoned me at the ruins.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Oh? Did I abandon you, or did I just walk ahead? I walk a great deal you know, and sometimes, my memories stay behind. \\n\\nI recall... a path you started to follow, but it was one I've already trodden.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Arcturus. Yes, that's what it's called. Is it a safe place? I believe it was once. \\n\\nYes, go there, and you will find sanctuary and guidance from those worthy to give it.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Again you return. Again that expectant look on your face. \\n\\nWhat misery do you bring to me? What answers did the tower provide?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 20,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Adiana_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Speaker of the Angry Earth",
        "Description": "Yonas Alazar says that if you want to become a Soulwarden, you'll need a living seed from the Angry Earth. Yonas recalls a woman in the wildnerness, elusive as a shadow, that may be able to help you acquire such a thing, if you can find her.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What if I became a Soulwarden?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "That is a… terrible idea. The process required to harden one's soul against Corruption demands a sacrifice you cannot imagine. \\n\\nThe days of the Soulwardens are done with, and I have a great deal of fishing to do…",
        "InProgressResponse": "Even if you do manage to track this huntress down, have no expectations. \\n\\nShe's not fond of other people, as I recall.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You tread on what was once hallowed ground, human. \\n\\nWhatever your purpose coming here, it is misguided. Go back to your settlement.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 20,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Adiana_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Adiana's Fountain",
        "Description": "Explore Canary Mine and purge whatever might be blocking the flow to Adiana's azoth fountain.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I came to ask a favor.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You are wasting your time and mine. \\n\\nWhat this land needs is fewer humans, time to heal… and a working azoth fountain. This one seems to be blocked.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The fountain still runs dry. That means you haven’t yet done as we asked. \\n\\nWas your offer insincere? Or do you lack the strength to follow through?",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well, the fountain is running again, so you've either been blessed with good fortune, or you actually followed through. \\n\\nI'm curious, however. What caused the blockage?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 20,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Adiana_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Weakness of the Ego",
        "Description": "Use Adiana's recipe to gather the ingredients to craft a tincture that will dampen the effects of Corruption.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I need a seed of the Angry Earth.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Hah. Do you even realize how much you ask? How much your kind has already taken? \\n\\nThe Angry Earth will want to know the truth: do you plan to use this seed to fight Corruption?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Have you made the tincture I taught you yet? You're going to need it.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "There now, that will afford you some protection, whether or not your request for the Seed is granted. \\n\\nI communed with the elements while you were away, but they have not yet given an answer.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 21,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Adiana_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "Azoth_Vessel",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Plans of the Pestilent",
        "Description": "Adiana Theron suspects the Corrupted of Ebonrock Armory are looking for something. Thin their forces and determine their purpose there.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What do I need to do?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The Ebonrock Caverns nearby are overrun with the Corrupted. \\n\\nWhile they may pose no direct threat to the Angry Earth, they are a scourge on the land.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Red eyes in the dark, watching night and day from the Ebonrock Caverns. \\n\\nPurge those you can and find out what it is they seek.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "My companion has told me all that transpired in the cavern. Not even I knew of the shrine the Angry Earth harbored there. \\n\\nThat they have succeeded in corrupting it is... troubling beyond measure.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 21,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "A Living Conduit",
        "Description": "Adiana Theron has seen fit to grant you a seed of power, a fitting conduit for the weapon of a Soulwarden. Return to Yonas Alazar with news of your success.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What does the seed do, exactly?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "It grants what your kind lacks - a connection to the earth itself. \\n\\nGive Yonas my regards. If he is your teacher, then you may yet defeat the darkness in your soul. Begone now, human.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You have what you need, so begone from here. \\n\\nThis is no longer a place for humans.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "It is a relief to see you return, {playerName}. Though my heart trembles to harbor hope again, it's too late to turn back. \\n\\nYou were able to get a living seed of the Angry Earth, then?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 21,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Last Cache",
        "Description": "In search of the haft for your Azoth Staff, Yonas indicates the existence a hidden, secret cache within the hidden interior of Canis.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"It's powered by my soul?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes. The relationship between azoth and the soul is complex, but it is this dynamic that gives a Soulwarden their strength. \\n\\nWhen focused through an azoth staff, it can perform many wonders.",
        "InProgressResponse": "We knew the tide was turning against us. \\n\\nI realize now, we created the caches in the hope that a day like this might arrive.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well now, it's been an age since I laid eyes on one of these. \\n\\nIt brings back many memories… not all of them painful either.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 23,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Argent and Aether",
        "Description": "Search the Ancient ruin of Vulcanus for the materials to craft the Crosspiece of your Azoth Staff.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Then where do I get one?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You can't. We had to melt them all down to make weapons during the last war. \\n\\nThe forge remains, however, and you may be able to create one yourself. I trust you are handy with a blacksmith's hammer?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Mind you tread lightly, young one. \\n\\nSuch places belong to the past, and the past has a habit of fighting back on this island.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I see you managed it after all. A fine crosspiece, almost as fine as Forgemaster Ezra once made. \\n\\nDid you have any trouble?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 24,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Reignition",
        "Description": "With the components of an ancient Soulwarden staff in hand, proceed to the forge beneath Shattered Obelisk. There, you will reignite the flame of the Soulwarden Order by bringing a new Azoth Staff into being.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Is she their leader?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I do not know. The traveler said the Corrupted rally around something called \"the Tempest,\" a being they worship like a god. \\n\\nIf it is this same being that haunts you, I fear your soul may be in great peril.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Find the altar near the Shattered Obelisk. \\n\\nThat is where the staff-forging ritual must take place.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Welcome back, {playerName}. And look at you! Still as fresh as a newborn babe. \\n\\nMost aspiring Soulwardens return looking at least a little pale. You must have extra soul to spare.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 24,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Captain",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_19a",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_19",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Hope in Your Hands",
        "Description": "Deliver news of hope to the people of Everfall. The staff in your hands carries with it the power to destroy Corruption at its roots.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We need to rally others to our cause.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I think so. Go back to Oxboro. Shout from the rooftops. Bang pots and pans if you must. \\n\\nRally their men and women at arms to meet the armies coming their way. You hold their only hope for salvation.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The strength of men will but stall the Corrupted threat. The staff you hold is the only way to permanently destroy the physical manifestations of Corruption. \\n\\nShow them the way forward.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ever since you went in search of your huntress, I've been plying everyone with a modicum of power to do something, anything, to prepare themselves for war. \\n\\nI confess, I am near to the end of my wits.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_19a",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Myth Made Weapon",
        "Description": "Though the townsfolk of Everfall refuse to help themselves, you have the means to protect them. Guard Captain Franc Dubois enlists your aid to defend the farms against the the growing threat of Corruption.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I have a weapon that can defeat Corruption.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Can such a thing exist? It feels too good to be true. Here we are teetering on the edge of disaster, and you conveniently have the answer? \\n\\nSorry, but I've patrolled the streets of Oxboro long enough to know this ruse.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Perhaps, with proof, I can finally convince this mess of a town to fight back.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "The staff has done its work- I can taste it in the air. Consecrated ground will repel the Corrupted for a time. \\n\\nI'd say you were born to be a Soulwarden, if that weren't such a tragic notion.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_21",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_20",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Destiny Unearthed",
        "Description": "Acquire a Heartgem, meant to shield your soul against the effects of Corruption. You can acquire allies to obtain a fallen Soulwarden's heartgem, or seek to create your own.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What's that?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "A Heartgem - a vessel you'll use to encase your soul, protect it, a cold vault within your chest. \\n\\nAnd the place you'll have to go to get one is a cold vault in the earth, beneath the Amrine Temple.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You should be able to open the Amrine temple door with that staff of yours. \\n\\nBring back the Heartgem, and we can finally start the ritual.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Look at that - an empty Heartgem. Almost brings a tear to my eye. \\n\\nTake a good look, because this thing is going to become part of you forever.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemSolo",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemSolo_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 4,
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_21_B",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_21_B_Unlock",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemSolo_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Forge Your Own Destiny",
        "Description": "Search southern Everfall for rare reagents needed to create a new Heartgem.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "",
        "InProgressResponse": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 25,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99A_Yonas_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_22",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_21",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Ritual",
        "Description": "Complete the ritual deep in Amrine Temple to conquer death and become a Soulwarden in full.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So I'll be immune to Corruption?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Not entirely. You can still fall to temptation or rage, but it offers protection, a buffer. \\n\\nSadly, it also buffers against the taste of food, the warmth of sunlight... the love of another. Are you sure you're ready?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Don't worry too much about the ritual. You know you're going to die, so it can't be any worse, can it? \\n\\nIn all honesty, it probably can, but let's pretend.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Welcome back, Soulwarden. You are now part of a legacy that goes back beyond the reach of history. \\n\\nYou have done more than surrender a life, you have surrendered your own soul. I salute your sacrifice.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99A_Faction_Vector",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 17,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99A_Faction_Vector_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99A_Faction_Vector",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99A_MSQ_01B",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99A_Faction_Vector_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "The Three Way War",
        "Description": "Neutrality is a dangerous prospect in these times. Seek out and speak to representatives from each of the warring factions to inform your choice of allegiance.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I will be careful.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Hold a moment. You look like someone who's handy with a weapon. \\n\\nI keep an eye out for such talents. If your allegiance hasn't already been claimed, there are those who'd like to change that.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I really do suggest you seek out the factions when you have time. \\n\\nFind out what they're all about and join up, if you're so inclined.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
